JAROMIR BACA

RESUME



-₩- Status

My name is Jaromir. I currently work as a reverse engineering specialist. Tree years ago I have decided to broaden my technical skills and thinking by enrolling to Information Security branch at BUT. By this, I achieved unique combination with background in mechanical and information technology engineering, cyber security and software law. Suitable for the industry 4.0. Now I am ready to start up a new episode of my career.

Work Experience

Reverse Engineering Specialist

MCAE Systems, 2016/02 – present

- ▶ 3D digitization for the generation CAD models from physical objects
- ▶ Responsible for quality and precision of CAD models for further production or development progress in Automotive and Aviation industry

CAD/CAM specialist, programmer, trainer

SolidVision, 2015/01 – 2015/12

- Conducted courses and presentation for current and potetial custumers
- ➤ Collaborated on design project of single purpose machines. Programmed NC codes for NC machines. Improvied my skills of SolidWorks to proficient level

CAD specialist and trainer for SolidWorks

3E Praha Engineering, 2014/09 – 2014/12

- Provided courses and customer support for SolidWorks users
- ▶ In charge of high quality of CAD models for the next production or development progress.

Education

Information Security specialist

VUT Brno, FEEC (ongoing)

- > This branch is focused on the area of general security in ICT technologies
- ▶ Acquiring theoretical knowledge of programming, OS, cyber security, economy and software law.

Mechanical Engineer

Secondary Mechanical Engineering School

- Focused on adopting technical thinking and ability to develope machines
- ➤ Theoretical and practical knowledge of heat treatment, machining and welding

I if you want to know more about me and my abilities, please don't hesitate to visit my profile on LinkedIn, GitHub or write me an email.

COTANCT/LINK

Prno, Czech Rep.

+420 602 583 018

igromirbaca88@gmail.com

github.com/StingrayCZ

in linkedin.com/in/jaromirbaca

MAIN TOOLS





OTHER TOOLS



Visual Studio IDE



Python



Java



Linux

LANGUAGE SKILLS





ENG, B2

GER, A1

ACTIVITIES







